Seino, hi - this is Shachi.
So, we are in the midst of the great year-end party of 2024,
The last video was more of us talking than expected, so we decided to split it into the first half and the second half.
Here is the second half.
What the heck, we did the third one.
Last time we started talking about staples,
We ended up doing two of them.
Were you able to look back to the middle of the second one?
Yes.
The story from Yuzuki's shuffle
Yes, the shuffle story.
We even got to the medley story.
The shuffle, Miss Mercy's
on the song "Hammer Rays".
Shuka-chan's costume and Shuka-chan's part.
I'm so happy to be here!
I'm so glad I got to be a part of it!
Stapella Fest didn't have Miss Mercy-chan, so
at this Stapa festival.
It was the first time for me to dance with Miss Mercy.
But Miss Mercy's dance was really difficult and there were so many of us.
That's exactly why Shuka is the best dancer. She was the best dancer.
She was a very young and rambunctious girl, so it was a little difficult to get everyone to dance together,
But Miss Mercy and her friends stayed behind to help us,
Oh, no?
They stayed and taught us. And it wasn't just one Miss Mercy, it was all of them,
We had a rehearsal where we had to shuffle around, and they would go to the rehearsal and then come back and teach us,
I really loved Miss Mercy, and I thought that I had to sing with absolute care, so I took on the challenge,
I hope you enjoyed it. I hope you enjoy it.
Yuzuki is the only one who can wear that costume. It was the most revealing ever. I was so surprised.
Maybe you mean that only Shuuka and Yuzuki can wear it? That's right. I wasn't used to seeing anyone else but Yuzuki.
It was quite a range, you know. But it looked good on her. You look beautiful. Thank you very much.
It was fun.
And that day?
That day, I, yes.
I'm not good at waiting.
That's right.
So, you said you became bad at waiting.
That's a good place to start.
Actually, this song, as an undercover project, has been in the works since before this summer.
Yeah, before the summer.
Before the summer.
That's right. With the name withheld.
We had posted the mv of the song on youtube, and at that stage, we had a great person working on it,
I was wondering if you would reveal the fact that we were the ones who made the video.
I thought you were not going to reveal it. We knew about it from the beginning.
If you talk about recording, it was long time ago. Yes, it was.
When can I say when this was done? It was over a year ago when we recorded it. We knew Ho-chan was filming, right?
So I wondered how this song was going to turn out. Finally, the staff collected the footage, and this is how it came to be.
Finally, we could see Ho-chan performing the song. We had heard that they were recording the song, but we had been asleep for about a year without knowing how it turned out.
I was a good dancer and so on.
I was a good dancer, and I was already a match.
But I had my own personality. Did I match?
More than I had heard. I was feisty, I stood out.
We had the right parts.
They told me not to laugh on that song.
Can you do it? You could?
It's really funny.
He was a witness. Even though he was told not to laugh.
I witnessed him being told to do it right before the show.
Was he told not to laugh like when?
No, they told me not to laugh from the recording.
Then, when Akimoto said, "I'm going to sing this song," I knew that I would laugh.
We would laugh at each other.
From the time of recording, we were told, "Don't put notes on it! I was told from the beginning of the recording session, "Don't put notes on it!
They said, "I'm sorry.
We were told we were in the garbage at the end.
Yeah, yeah. It's gone, so that it doesn't ring.
It's the one that's on public display now.
And the choreography?
It was the day before my birthday when I choreographed it.
Even then
They kept saying, "Expressions, expressions, expressions.
You were there during the choreography.
That's right.
The teachers.
One of the teachers was watching the choreography.
He called me over.
Honoka! Aiara! Hinoka! Stop laughing!
Right!
Ah!
Hinoka! Honoka! You don't seem to laugh.
She does.
Maybe she has the same attribute as Hou-chan. She's up even though she's not laughing.
That's true.
It's an advertisement.
It's a little bit like "I'm curious about it. You have to consciously avoid it.
Right before the show and before we left, when Rika-chan was explaining the song to us, we were all in the back.
I said I was sorry if I laughed too hard, and we all left.
But when I saw the video, the memories were so great.
I was told too much.
Before the show, there was a small corridor with a raised area in the corner where we could sit down one at a time,
There was a place where five people could normally sit if they sat side by side, but Ho-chan's teacher was sitting facing me, sitting on the floor in a mountain pose,
I wondered why he was sitting on a mountain, too.
I wondered what he was doing.
I was wondering what he was doing.
I wonder what he's doing.
I wondered what they were doing.
I would listen in while taking selfies and other things on TikTok.
Then I'd say, "Don't laugh, really!
I really shouldn't laugh, I shouldn't laugh.
I had a little girl I loved for a long time.
I loved her so much, she really passed away.
Yes, she sang with a sad face.
Ha-ha-ha!
LOL.
It's like he's thinking something.
Laughing...
I was thinking that too.
LOL.
I keep looking at that and I keep coming up with that.
The look on Honoka's face when she's being told that is amazing.
She has to be able to express herself and sing!
The teacher is pretty passionate about it too.
It was a real challenge for me.
The tune of the song, the dance, the facial expressions, everything was a challenge.
But it was a nice accent.
Thank you very much.
It was such an
That's funny.
And you're good at that too, aren't you, Ho-chan?
That kind of unit
And Supapla, too.
I've already been on location.
I'd like to introduce it to everyone in the country, you know.
I'd like to introduce it to everyone in the country.
I like it.
You're talking a lot about red, too, aren't you?
No, not red.
The make-up artist is always scared of it.
When there's an interview, and I have some free time...
There are times when we have to do interviews, right?
When there are 3 hours between interviews.
Hon-chan suddenly says...
You know how you say, "I'm going to go get dressed now"?
The makeup artist said, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
The makeup artist's ready to go!
Stop everything! We'll have to redo all the makeup.
Yeah, you're making me sweat.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can see you're scared a lot.
That's how much I like you.
This is the unit that Team Girl 2 shuffled into for this show.
This show?
Yes, it is.
Oh, yeah. Sniper.
Sniper's 10th show.
She did it.
She's Basho no Chan-seta.
I'm Yuno-chan from Ebitu-chan.
I'm Iichi-chan.
Iichi-chan
And Rine-chan
I'm so happy!
Look at that, it's just Nagoya!
Eh, it was heavy!
Yes, it's true, it was heavy.
I'm glad you went to Jimoti.
And Ichi, with the two guys from Localism, she's pretty good.
This is the first time she's been in this level.
So many feelings...
I was so happy that I felt like I had crossed the waterfall.
I'm glad you guys went.
Our costumes were completely different.
It was the first time I'd ever seen them dance on stage.
With the audience in attendance...
Oh, Shach? But I'm here.
It was a weird feeling.
It's like... when we shuffle around and everyone's in different outfits...
And when they're in uniform, I'm judging them by their outfits.
It's like, "Oh my God, we're on stage!
There was one time when people were coming and going.
I thought it's so important to wear a costume to find people.
It was hard. I didn't know.
I see. Costumes are very powerful.
Yuna, she's been looking at you the whole time, so she was really cool.
You were cool.
Like, "I'll always be watching you.
So cool!
I learned that pattern.
I'm going to incorporate a little bit of it.
The non-open version.
"I'll be watching you all the time.
Maybe it's a little different.
Yuzu was close.
I can't do it.
The streaming, it's still in the archives.
You can watch it over and over again.
I'll study it.
The atmosphere changes a lot, doesn't it?
When the members change...
It's totally different.
It's amazing to be able to express your individuality.
You can express your own style even with different songs.
I was so happy.
Thank you very much.
And the last comment
You did 3 shows!
That's right.
In the three performances
It was a grade by grade eye picture.
How do you talk?
Oh, no!
My mouth gets dry.
I can't do it for three shows.
I can't do it even if it's 3 shows.
I'd like to have a finale... but I'm too old... and there's only a little meat left.
And since it was a medley by grade, the three of us were the same age, so we were on the same team, only in spring we were different.
We were all in uniforms, but we were all on the same team, so we did the medley because we wanted to be on the same team.
Oh, no...
ah?
But it was fun to watch because we were all in the same grade.
It was fun to watch, wasn't it?
I guess you were the older generation on the staff, right?
So, you know, we've shared our experiences with each other.
It's different to be in a group with people you've shared so much history with.
It's very emo.
We've seen similar history.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
So, by grade level...
There were 97 of us.
It's surprisingly small.
Oh, really?
There were only four of you?
Only Mire-chan was in the group.
Almost.
Almost all orcas.
Mire-chan was the entertainer, so we were all together.
So it's all the same.
Shachi
Haru's flow is the same.
So we were all looking at it from an objective point of view.
Oh, so there wasn't
That's right.
We're both entertainers, Mire-chan and I.
We're close when we're in the groove.
We're comfortable with each other.
If it's the same as usual...
If it's not the same as usual...
We can stand there and listen to them sing.
There's no dialogue.
The music is good.
It's so, so, so tiny.
It's called "Where is the Star Wind?
I was so nervous.
I was so nervous. It's the only song I haven't danced to. I didn't really dance to it.
And it was in the audience, so everyone was standing close to each other.
So there was a lot of tension. And there were some "hamoris" (harmonies), too.
So Mire-chan did all the harmonies.
That's right, that's right.
Mire-chan and Yuki did the upper and lower parts.
Mire-chan was the only one who did mine.
Mire-chan did everything.
Amazing!
She became a beacon for me.
She was doing the lower part right before her part.
But she came right back for her part.
Amazing!
It was a difficult song, but I'm glad he did it.
Also, a behind-the-scenes story from 1997 is that when they were choreographing the song, which wasn't us, Kaja was playing the next song, "Kaya," which was by Faraway-san,
Kaya, Kaya from afar, told us at rehearsal that she was born in 1997,
She says, "I was born in '95," and everyone gets upset.
Kaya!
As soon as she comes back.
No one is 25 years old!
I'll be older than Aaryn and Rika.
I'm just Simbio around here.
I'm not there, so I'm not 7.
They'll get it wrong...!
I said I'm turning 29
I turned one this year.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thirty-seven. Ninety-seven.
Four of you, you're not going to go down the hallway.
Kaede!
That was scary.
Those four look scary.
Mire-chan was curious too
When grandma first introduced them...
I bet she got scared.
I'm sure they were scared. She said.
It's not often you see Kanya scared.
You don't see that very often.
It's scary when he walks with the wind on his shoulders.
Scary, scary.
That's what happened to me, and spring was in '98,
Aya, that's right, Haru was born in '99.
Oh, really?
That's right.
I know she was born in '99.
During the rehearsal, I told them that the girl who would fall in front of Spring was born in 1998.
I also said, "It's the 8th year, but it's not the 8th year.
It's not spring.
I'm going to have to ask you to put it on a little bit.
Why is it still
You've got a girl on you.
Every year is more serious
I thought it'd be fine for Haru to be 2 now.
But she's 1 year old and not that different
It's only 2 months old
I don't know how I'm going to get them to let me in
I'm not sure how I'm going to get him in.
The three points were funny.
I remember now.
The age is pretty serious, so don't make the mistake of making a mistake, folks.
I like 7th grade and 8th grade.
When I say "Haru", I mean "FY8".
Please like the 8th grade.
That was funny.
So, Haru, right?
Using Aya-chan's lucky number
While enjoying Aya-chan's singing voice
I'll put this in at the end
Nabe no shime ramen
The name is exactly as it sounds
Just simmer it well
After all, we want to have "shime" in the pot
I want it!
I like the noodles the best
Thank you so much for making it.
I hope I did it right.
That's right.
We'll do it in the spring. We'll do it by grade level.
That's right! In the spring, we did Soranbushi.
But this time we're going to do a different grade, and we're going to have songs by our friends who've been through it all together, like Kurako-chan's "Bamboo Shoots" and Takonji-chan's "Carnaval"...
And this time, by grade, we've included songs by our friends who have been through it all together.
Carnaval is a song of the generation that used to work with Takojichan, even though it was Soranbushi in the spring.
You used to come to see us every time, right, Mr. Reha?
That's why she said it was so emo and cried.
Yeah, but she cried, said she was so happy, and gave me a line after she came back.
He said he was so happy to see me at Karunavalet, and he came to see me every time.
You know, I think I was crying the hardest.
I got all emo, too.
Takoniji was six months older than me. We're almost the same age.
We've been working together locally for a long time, so I was the most moved.
I was so close... and the members who were chosen were... what do you call them?
I know that they know you better than the younger members.
That's why... the members who knew him back then sang the song.
We're happy too. Yuki Budoko has changed.
Seriously, was that too much love? I really feel like I'm at peace with the world.
I was having so much fun, you know the walkie-talkie the staff uses in the back?
I was playing with it for a bit, and all the staff members were talking on it.
I told them I was looking forward to the bamboo shoot gnocchi.
Kanamin replied, saying thank you and that she would do her best.
Even in that walkie-talkie, the staff was probably a little relaxed.
I know, right?
But I really.
I got on the elevator after the meeting, and Kanamin and then Ai-chan were there, and Kanamin politely reported everything to Ai-chan.
I was just at the staff's place, and Manaka-chan said she was looking forward to the show the most.
So cute.
I'm good friends with her.
I knew her from her Instagram and stuff, so I guess that's what I saw more.
We were like "detonchy-dee" too, you know?
I watched a lot of Bamboo Shoot Gnocchi on the streaming, and I felt like I had to be at the end of the next song of Bamboo Shoot Gnocchi,
But Bamboo Shoot Gnocchi was so cute that it was getting a little late.
Oh yeah, I was watching the streaming and it was time for me to leave.
Stop it!
You started at the beginning.
There was the pandelator, right?
And then after that...
And then there's Soran.
It's a soran, Spring!
Haru took the lead.
He led that many people.
Everyone learned the songs from the last three shows.
Everyone was doing their own thing.
That's the one you struggled with the most.
That's right.
We were struggling, too.
Usually it takes me one time to learn a song.
One time.
And then we would start to solidify it on our own.
But for this Solar Clause, we actually made a Solar Clause, and if we had Mr. Kasuga, who is doing it, we would have had a lot of money.
If I had put it on the Kasuga-san who is doing it, I would have had to pay a lot of money.
So, I don't have the steps I've taken in the 10 years I've been working as a shirt maker.
We do the footwork and the shaking off in three days...
We do it in three days.
It's difficult to watch the video and memorize it by ourselves.
The sound is difficult.
It's not about counting.
We had a mayhem supplies class together during rehearsal.
They worked really hard on that.
It's hard to sing, too. It's just dancing.
That's right. But everyone worked so hard.
They were kind of happy, you know, with our music.
So many kids, you know, taking it so seriously.
It was a festival, a medley of birds.
They were so fired up.
They were really fired up.
That was great.
I came here to laugh.
Yeah, in the Love Chima.
It was great to hear that.
I only get to hear it in the spring.
It's not easy to do, so I thought, "I'm going to do my best.
That's great.
I could hear Kamae's voice echoing all over the place.
Kamae!
It was echoing all over the place.
I don't need this.
But, you know, we haven't used it yet.
Let's do a little more.
Let's give it a couple more minutes.
Maybe it's still attached.
If we do it...
So, do the medley.
Shuffle?
That's right.
Give me a little more.
Thank you.
That was my day.
I did the shuffle.
Like Uka-chan's Monday raffle.
It's...
That's...
Mr. Shiro's title.
I was so happy because it was my favorite song.
I see a lot of Uka-chan.
That's nice.
Uka-chan-like?
Me too.
The pink in your outfit really suited you.
I loved that outfit.
It looked great on you.
I took so many pictures with it.
I wore so many different outfits for three days.
Why didn't you take any ticks?
I only took ticks of Uka-chan's outfit.
It was my favorite.
It's so cute that I wanted to take a picture of it even in the midst of a flurry of activity.
That outfit.
Already, that one, Ayaka's.
What? What? I saw it.
Did you see it?
She was so cool, with her long tones.
Ayaka is really amazing.
She's amazing.
She said that too.
We were doing something like that together.
Yes, together, we were really listening to it through ear monitors.
I was thinking, how can I say it, not only are you good at it, but your expression,
I thought that expression was only up to this point,
But Ayaka, I'm going here.
I don't know,
Your range is amazing. My concept of width changed when I heard Aya's voice.
Moreover, Aya's fake music was arranged a little differently,
Here's the arrangement, too. I saw the members of Unka, too, and they were like, wow.
The group being covered also learned a lot.
This shuffle unit project
I'm impressed. I was moved the whole time we were doing it.
Mako-chan was great, too, wasn't she? Ume-chan, too.
Sora-chan taught us all the shaking off.
Instead of having a male teacher teach me, you taught me everything from 1 to 100.
She was so kind.
Did she teach you in her spare time?
We were rehearsing a bit and the teacher was on the exclusive side.
So she stayed behind and said I'll teach you during this time.
She taught me everything.
Because, you know, there's hardly any free time anymore, it was a rehearsal environment.
Yeah, yeah.
And they all taught me in just a few minutes, you know, in that environment,
I wondered why they were all such good kids.
That was one wonderful thing.
I simply thought, "That's wonderful.
They were wonderful.
Yes, good people.
And, you know, Tull, too.
There's also Tull, right?
Yes.
Oh, exclusive.
Yeah.
Yurichi-chan performed when she wore them. It was Emma's part, so she got to wear the orange outfit.
It was something new and fresh, but you looked great in that outfit.
Orange makes me feel brighter. I didn't know the color of the costume could change.
But it was still social skills. Social power everywhere.
The members were saying that to me earlier. I recognized it even though it was a different color.
I could tell even though there were so many of us. I'm glad.
It was fun. It was like we were in our youth when we met. I was looking at them so much and singing.
You were so happy when we met. I was so happy because it was me,
It was fun. You seemed to be having fun. I could feel it.
I love it.
So, did you do SNS in the spring?
Yes, we had SNS on that day.
What do you think?
There was a new song called Sugar Non Sugar!
It was so cute!
So we performed a song called "Praise Me".
It's a new song!
Yes, a new song.
We had a new song.
That's right.
On social networking sites.
It's a social networking site selection.
Everyone was so cute.
They were cute from the rehearsal.
The choreography this time was by Sako Maki, and as a shirt, I was invited twice by Sako, so I was able to see Sako-san more often, but this time
Ira was the only one I had met before, but everyone else I had met before.
I had met her before, and she pretended that I was Sako-san, and I pretended to be Sako-san.
And Sako-san's pretending is cute, too. She takes the cuteness that each of us has and makes it look even cuter!
The traffic was jam-packed from the Japanese point of view, and the cuteness was so strong.
The characters were so strong. Everyone was amazing, because they are active on social networking sites. They all had a bright aura, you know?
Everyone seemed to be looking at me. The way you showed it. The way they showed it when they were on the screen was wonderful.
You must be used to it. It was amazing.
The way they showed it. I love the music so much.
It's so cute. I want to hear the music again.
It's a new song.
That's all? Once you look back?
These two sides are done? Eat up, eat up.
I can finally look back. That's great.
I knew it. It's only third class. It's not what it looks like.
They did it in two days. That's amazing.
That's amazing.
It's amazing!
I felt so relieved when I could see the members during the whole song.
I was so happy!
You can finally meet them there.
The timeline is so different,
This girl is in the fall, but this girl is on stage at that time,
That's just not true.
Thank you.
I was a little happy and a little sad at the same time.
I was happy that someone was there when I went back to school.
Oh, you're here.
I thought, "You're here.
That was fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yuzuki was the MC for all three shows.
That's right.
Thank you.
Tired
When I had a trouble with my Japanese in the middle of the show
Haruka helped me out.
She translated it for me.
I knew you could understand what I was saying.
I got it.
Haru didn't get it at all.
But to Teku...
What?
There were first-timers, too.
Some of them don't even know who Killer Whales are.
That's right.
There were kids who didn't know.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
I ate it.
It was warm enough to take the noodles.
Thank you, Haru.
I want to put it in.
Thank you.
Here are the noodles.
It's the end of the meal
Thank you very much.
I got it, actually.
Please eat.
You're a good eater.
Is the food good?
Is it a good ending?
Come on, come on.
It's good.
The noodles are so soft.
The soup goes really well with them.
That's right.
I bet the staff is crazy about this.
I want you to try the noodles.
I want you to eat it. There's so much to choose from.
You two are doing the long rope.
There was a game.
There was a long rope.
But listen, they made it sound like you're really good at the long rope,
I'm good at it.
They were introduced as if they were good at long rope and that they wanted to be in the game.
The audience was excited and said, "We're going to do it.
Everyone backstage was making announcements, or rather, responding to the MC, or to the script,
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't know when we were chosen for the big rope,
I like it, but I don't remember when we did it.
We couldn't practice separately for each team, so it was almost our first time.
So we didn't get to practice separately for the first time.
So, the a-team was very good, right?
The C-team was amazing, we went 40 times.
That's great!
Team A went about 20 times.
And then the B team went 10 times.
That's why... Sembricha.
Forty times is amazing.
That's right.
Because, you know, we were all supposed to take 1,000.
Yeah, yeah.
Amazing!
You're a good spinner, too.
Did the members pass it around?
Yeah.
Just the spinning.
So you have to include the spinning rope.
We had three seven-person teams.
But I don't know...
I don't know... the person who spins the rope isn't drinking the tea.
Why?
Is that a mistake?
What was that?
Flying?
He's doing it to the staff.
What's that?
What's that? It's a team hack.
Everyone on all three teams is supposed to be the person who spins the same rope.
They're hacked into teams.
But only two of the ropes, Wakabayashi and Ai-chan...
Wakabayashi and Ai-chan, were standing next to each other with an apologetic look on their faces.
They were on the same team.
That's not good.
At first I thought it was a mistake.
I thought I simply forgot to prepare it.
I heard there was a penalty game.
I'm not talking about that anymore.
I'm sure everyone drinks.
Yeah, you don't, not really.
It's just the rope.
What?
It's a lot of work just to turn it.
No, it's harder to fly.
It's harder to fly.
It's harder to drink.
That's right.
I've been saying, "Why don't you drink it?
I kept saying, "Why don't you drink it?
I know, right?
So they weren't a team.
I mean, they're not a team.
As the mouse.
And I feel sorry for them.
Let's say goodbye to them.
Now?
Two.
Let's get them together first.
I'll see you later.
Each.
I'll send them to Tohoku and Fukuoka for the election.
I see.
I had to say goodbye to Ai.
You should do an insta-live or something.
Yeah, connect.
Have a drink.
Okay.
Oh, man! He's too commanding!
Too scary!
Don't you like me?
I don't hate you too much.
Really, it's still a little bit of a mess.
That's not good!
You shouldn't leave a little bit of a mess.
That's right.
I think it's a good idea to have a meeting with the check-embattler, and have the Estim staff come in and think about it, and then the conductor can take charge of it.
I'd like you to take charge of it, Mr. Conductor, so that we can avoid any bad decisions.
I don't know... why you call it a misjudgment.
And by mistake, you mean the only thing that was bothering you, right?
Aaah!
I'm sure you're thinking this is all over, but if you're bitter, it means that before the concert, you were trying to get Dad's attention, and he was trying to get you excited.
I'm sure you've been doing a lot of perky stuff before the show, like the "anti-tea cup" that's supposed to be a kind of "silent" cup.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'd like to try it.
I usually drink tea... it's kinda bitter... but he's being nice to me.
You thought? At the time...
I thought it was very bitter.
You thought so.
Well, congratulations, you're on the staff now.
If you drink it with that in mind, you'll get a very strong taste.
The concentration is definitely different.
Change the concentration, Senbridge.
Hana-chan was on the same team.
Wasn't that dangerous?
Hana-chan never says that.
Hana-chan's basically the type to accept things.
You never say things like that.
Isn't that a little bit dangerous?
She was saying that on the way home.
They changed their ways again.
With Hana-chan around, it's pretty bad.
And you think it's bitter?
It was rather bitter.
It stayed in my mouth for a long time.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that makes it more confusing.
There's a girl who didn't drink.
Yeah, and if there were two of them, it would be more...
That's a lie.
I mean, there could have been.
Bitterness.
I'm not the one who decided that I didn't need to drink with those two girls.
I don't know, but I'm not going to let you leave the place without a warm drink.
I'm going to go get a hot drink.
It's going to spread, and it's in my mouth, but it's still there.
Who's that?
That's not the director.
It was like that. It was fun.
It was a lot of work.
It was a lot of work, but everyone was happy, and I'm glad we did it. It was the first one.
It was the first time we did the SNS medley, and the TikTok medley.
We were able to visit many places, and that was fun, too.
I've never been to such a slow tour before.
I got lost a few times.
Everyone got lost.
I don't know, someone said, "Please wait for me! Someone was saying, "Please wait for me!
Someone was saying "Mai, come here!" with a microphone or something.
Did she say that?
Yes, I did.
Oh, I want to hear it.
There's only one of us, so Nao will be doing the dance.
Please wait for me!
I'll finish with the next song! I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting for you,
We had decided on the route,
But time was running out, and everyone was serving, so it was getting slower and slower and slower.
I thought, "How am I going to get back to the stands when the next song is coming up and I'm not even in the stands?
I thought, "You'll never be there.
Thank you, I couldn't have come back if you hadn't led me.
You were so stubborn and determined, weren't you?
There were so many memories.
Even though... you might still be able to see the show... and I can see it... but... please watch it... for those of you who couldn't make it.
I looked back at the staff and I'm glad you were able to see it.
I'm glad you were able to see it.
Yes, I hope so.
I would like to expand this circle.
I think we also learned how cute everyone is, and we learned more about the good qualities of each person.
I thought it was a great idea.
I thought so.
I'm glad we did it.
It's full of charm.
Yes, it's full of charm.
You did that?
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button, comment and subscribe to our channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye!